Line 1
Line 2
Realization: What did you notice about the file and commit history after reset? I realize that I am currrently in line 3 when I echo it, then the previous file I did was adding Line 2 message inside the file.txt.. to recover the previous append I did which Line 2, I use its commit ID after the git --oneline command and I did moved the HEAD to the previous commit which is appending Line 2, and the latest text I put which is line 3 disappeared.
