Line 1
Line 2
My realization was the difference of reset to revert is not removing entirely the last changes to its history. I saw that the Add Line 3 message with its commit ID is still in the history when I did the revert. While when I reset it, the HEAD moves to the next commit changes before the current commit I removed. Also, in the HEAD of revert thing, it is automatically stated that I reverted the last commit I did, while in reset it just remove the last commit changes I did and disappeared entirely in the history.
